Dhinesh D

dhineshdhamodharan07@gmail.com



+91-7904923362

Career Overview

To build upon my present knowledge and to contribute towards the growth of professionally managed organization with my skills and experience, leading towards my growth and development.

Certifications

- Completed 'Full-stack developer' course in GUVI Geek Network Pvt. Ltd.
- Completed JavaScript course in GUVI.
- Completed GIT course in GUVI.

Technical Skills

- ➤ HTML
- > css
- JavaScript
- React JS
- Node JS
- Mongo DB

Professional Experience

- Prodapt Solutions Private Ltd, Chennai January 2014 to 2020.
- Sreyas Datamatics Private Limited, Coimbatore July 2020 to October2020.

Education Summary

Completed Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering (First class) from VSB Engineering College, Karur during 2009-2013

Links

➤ Git-hub : https://github.com/dhineshdhamodharan

Portfolio : https://dhineshdhamodharan-portfolio.netlify.app/

Linked-in: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dhinesh-dhamodharan-44a2831a2

Personal Information

Date of Birth : 14th Jan 1992

Nationality : Indian
Sex : Male

Marital Status : Married

Current Address : 7/55-3 Sri Balaji Garden 5th street Karattumedu, Saravanampatti, Coimbatore-641035

Permanent Address : Dhinesh, S/o Dhamodharan, Puthu Street, Kalambur.

Languages Known : English, Tamil.

Declaration

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Place:

Date: (D. DHINESH)